As you can see, there is quite a bit of damage.
As you can see here, granules have filled up your gutters.
These granules are supposed to be what's protecting your home.
When wind and hail hits your roof,
it knocks out these granules,
which reduces the lifespan of your roof.
This is very similar to damage to the rest of the approvals
we've gotten in the area.
With that being said,
insurance companies are always looking for ways
to mitigate their losses.
It's unfortunate, but that's how they make money.
The most important part of this process
is that when your insurance company comes out
to run their inspection,
we are here as storm experts
to make sure you as a homeowner get a fair shake.
If they are missing anything,
we make sure they see all the damage that I just showed you.
What I'm going to do now is run to my car,
grab my iPad, and we can get this process started.